Entonces, oye.
Don't be so shy.
Everyone,
this is...
Spencer.
Yeah, that's right, Spencer.
Nice to meet you, Spencer.
Henry, what's going on here?
Dad, hold on.
Go ahead.
Everyone is waiting.
I'm...
Gina's... ex-fiancé.
Let's get to the point.
What's your name again?
Spencer.
My name is Spencer.
Yeah, That's right.
Spencer, let's get to the point.
Okay.
I begged Gina to have children,
but she can't.
She's, infertile.
Unfortunately.
And in case anyone
thinks Spencer is lying.
Here, her medical records.
Oh, yeah.
Appreciate your time.
Good luck.
Thank you.
Now it's family business.
Bye, Steve.
Hey.
You're mistaken.
We just received a certificate
from the doctor.
She's pregnant with my child.
Gina's pregnant with my child.
Come on, Walt.
Is it really that hard for someone
as powerful as you
to get doctor's signature?
Especially
at a hospital
we're stuffing
millions of dollars
I don't understand any of this.
Gina, can you have children or not?